《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24.
找到毒气罐了吗
Have you secured the canister?
阁下  恐怕还没有
I'm afraid not, ma'am.
我们的疑犯逃出了封锁线
Our suspect escaped beyond the perimeter.
你们不是说封锁那区域了吗
I was told that the area was locked down.
-怎么回事  -他有帮凶
- What happened? - He had help
是托尼·阿尔梅达
From Tony Almeida.
阿尔梅达
Almeida?
他为我们做事的啊
He was working for us.
这只是表象
It only appeared that way.
他显然是在执行自己的计划
Apparently he was pursuing his own agenda,
想要弄到毒气罐
Trying to get his hands on the canister.
我们已召集所有人员重新部署寻找线索
We're all regrouping to develop leads.
我可能有一条线索
I may have one.
在霍奇斯被拘捕时
As hodges was taken into custody,
他叫嚣说  在他被捕后
He yelled at me about some larger group
还有更大的组织会继续行动
That would continue on after his arrest.
我们得跟他谈谈
We need to talk to him.
打电话给司法部长
I need you to call the attorney general
起草一份给乔纳斯·霍奇斯的证人保护协议
And draft a witness protection agreement for Jonas Hodges.
没有别的让他开口的法子了
There's no other way he'll talk.
你的亲生儿子死在他手里  更不要提
This man murdered your son, not to mention
数以百计的无辜平民
Hundreds of innocent civilians.
有什么我可以为你做的吗
Is there anything else that I can do for you?
杀了乔纳斯·霍奇斯之外  我别无他求
Other than kill Jonas Hodges, no.
我不是这个意思
I didn't mean that.
你是对的
You know, you're right.
我们不该在电话里讨论这个
We shouldn't be talking about this over the phone.
你什么时候能到白宫
How soon can you be at the White House?
-15分钟怎么样  -很好
- How's 15 minutes sound? - Good.
我们计划在明年初
The plan was to launch simultaneous attacks
对多个大城市发动同步攻击
Early next year in multiple cities,
公众就会意识到  政府无法保全他们
So the public would finally see that the government can't protect them.
他们会要求采取果断举措  我们就乘虚而入
They'd demand drastic measures, and we'd step in.
我们会支持那些想摧毁这个国家的敌人
We were going to supply the enemies that want to destroy this country.
张三李四王二麻子
Muhammed this, Achmed that.
霍奇斯先生  我要你说出同党的名字
Mr. Hodges, I need the names of the people that you are working with.
-我没有  -我要名单
- I don't have them. - I want the names.
我真不知道
I don't know any!
我们只需今天再发动一次袭击
Another attack today is all we need
就能让整个事态发展到崩溃的边缘
To push this thing right over the edge.
现在绝不是撤退的时候
This is no time to pull back.
我建议我们今天就拿着毒气罐
I say we take that canister
-去完成任务  -我联系一下组织
- And finish the job off today. - I'll contact the group.
这次行动会被归咎于这个人
The attack will be attributed to this man--
吉布安·阿尔扎利安
Jibraan Al-zarian.
我们讨论的是几个小时之内
We're talking about launching a new operation
展开一次新行动
In the next few hours
却只凭一个毒气罐
And with only one canister.
行动计划早就有了
The plan for this operation was already in place.
我们只不过是加快了点脚步
We'd just be accelerating the timetable.
乔纳斯·霍奇斯是一个我型我素的人
Jonas Hodges was a loose cannon,
现在组织已经成功地除掉了他
And the group is well rid of him,
但他疯狂的行为  对我们倒不无益处
But, in his lunacy, he did us a favor.
我们要抓住这次机会
I say we take it.
哈米德
Hamid!
闭嘴就没事
Keep your mouth shut and no one gets hurt.
-明白了吗  -是的
- You understand?! - Yes!
以下情节发生在凌晨4点至5点间
The following takes place between 4 a.m. and 5 a.m.
你还需要多久
How much more time do you need?
资料快下载完了
The material's almost finished downloading.
财务记录也准备好了
Financial records are in place.
我还需要15分钟来更改时间戳印
I'm gonna need about another 15 minutes to alter the time stamps.
很好
Good.
我现在把封条撕下来
I'm gonna take this off.
你要敢叫  你跟你弟弟就没命了
You yell for help, you and your brother die.
明白吗
Understand?
你们是什么人
Who are you people?
你们把宣扬伊斯兰圣战的东西放进我电脑
You're putting Jihadi propaganda on my computer.
还有这些武器  你们
These weapons-- you're...
你们想让我看起来像个恐怖分子
You're trying to make me look like a terrorist.
你们为什么要这样做
Why are you doing this?
吉布安  听我说
Listen to me, jibraan.
你只需要知道一件事
There's only one thing you need to know.
如果你不照我说的做
If you don't do exactly as I say,
你会眼睁睁看着你弟弟死在你面前
You're going to watch your younger brother die right in front of your eyes.
然后  我也会杀了你
And then... I'm gonna kill you.
但是  如果你合作
However... if you cooperate...
你们两兄弟有可能活下来
...there's a good chance the two of you will live through this.
你想要我做什么
What do you want me to do?
首先
First off...
你要面对摄像机念这段声明
You're going to read this statement in front of a camera,
要念得有诚意
And you're going to read it like you mean it.
不  这太扯淡了
No, this is insane.
我不能念这个
I can't read this.
我不干
I'm not going to do this.
好啊  听起来你好像觉得自己还有的选了
Okay, see, that sounds to me like you think you have a choice.
求你了  这样不对
Please, this is not right.
你不能这么对我们
You can't do this to us.
好吧
Okay, fine.
好  好  求你不要伤害他
Okay, okay, please, please don't hurt him.
我会照你说的做
I'll do whatever you say.
好吗
Okay?
给你5分钟把那看一遍
I'll give you five minutes to look that over.
我刚用反恐组服务器完成了第一次扫描
I just finished the first sweep with the CTU servers.
完全检测不到有什么活动或聊天记录
There's been no chatter, no activity at all.
你更新监视名单了吗
You updated the watch list?
更新了  名单上所有人
Yes, everyone on that list
都已经在执法机构监视下了
Is already under surveillance by law enforcement.
如果有人要干点什么
If one of them was gonna do something,
我们早就发现了
We would know about it.
可恶  我们得扩大搜索范围
Damn, well, we're going to have to widen our parameter.
扩大到什么程度
To include what?
我要你检查华盛顿市区范围的所有穆斯林
I want you to check out every muslim in the Washington D.C. area.
目标是敏感职位的政府工作人员
Target anyone who's working in a sensitive government position
或是可能受到袭击的区域的人员
Or in a place that might get hit.
然后调出在穆斯林社区工作的
Then I want you to start pulling the files
所有政治活动家的档案
On every political activist working in the muslim community.
还有  联系移民规划局
Also, I want you to contact INS.
我想要最近从伊斯兰国家来的移民名单
I want a list of every recent immigrant from an islamic country.
抱歉  有人听到种族成见的话了吗
Excuse me, has anybody heard of racial profiling?
詹尼斯  别说了
Janis, not now.
不  她是对的
No, she's right.
你是对的  这是种族成见
You're right, this is racial profiling,
我跟你一样都不喜欢
And I don't like it any more than you do,
但霍奇斯明确告诉我
But Hodges told me specifically
他会利用穆斯林激进分子
That he was going to utilize muslim extremists
转移人们对这次袭击的责难对象
In an effort to offload the blame for this attack.
我得知道他的同党是谁
I need to know who he's working with,
我们没时间了
And we're running out of time.
我不知道还有什么更好的办法
I don't know a better way of doing this.
如果你有  请现在就告诉我
So if you do, please tell me now.
没有
No.
好吧  谢谢
Okay, thank you.
克罗伊  请你追查那个列表中的
Chloe, I need you to run down the list of...
抱歉
I-I'm sorry,
我忘了我要说的话了
I forgot what I was saying.
移民规划局记录  杰克
INS records, jack?
没错  先追查那些记录再逆向追踪
Yeah, run those down first and then work backwards.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
这是他第二次这样了
This is the second time he's done this.
他总是忘东西  脸色很差
He keeps forgetting things, he looks like hell.
这种情况下  他干得很不错了
He's doing pretty well, considering.
这种情况
Considering?
什么情况
Considering what?
他没告诉你吗
He didn't tell you?
告诉我什么
Tell me what?
如果杰克有什么问题
If there's something wrong with jack,
现在就告诉我
Tell me now.
他病了  克罗伊
He's sick, Chloe.
他感染了阮病毒变体
He was infected with the prion variant.
怎么感染的
How?
他当时想要夺回生化武器罐子
He was trying to recover the bioweapon canisters
其中一个破裂了
And one of them ruptured.
他暴露在了毒气中
He was exposed.
我的天哪
Oh, my god.
抱歉  克罗伊  他可能不想让你担心
I'm sorry, Chloe, he probably didn't want you to worry.
克罗伊
Chloe...
你为什么不告诉我你病了
Why didn't you tell me you were sick?
这不要紧
It doesn't matter.
不要紧
It doesn't matter?
我是你朋友
I'm your friend.
我们得专心找托尼
We need to stay focused on finding Tony.
杰克  你应该去医院
Jack, you should be in the hospital.
这病无法治疗
There's no treatment for this.
无药可医
There's no cure.
你是说你会死
So you're telling me you're dying?
是的
Yes.
还有多少时间
How long?
一天  或者两天
A day, maybe two.
我一直在打抗痉挛的药让自己撑着
I've been taking this anti-seizure medicine to keep me on my feet.
目前都还管用
It's been working so far.
老天
Oh, my god.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
克罗伊  没事的
Chloe, it's all right.
我已经接受了现实
I've accepted it...
我也需要你这样做
and I need you to accept it, too.
不管还能活多久  我希望能做点事
Whatever time I've got left, I want it to matter.
我们得找到托尼  了结此事
We need to find Tony, put an end to this.
克罗伊
Chloe.
没有你  我做不到的
I can't do this without you.
拜托了  我需要你回去继续工作
Please, I need you to go back to work.
好吧
Okay.
我们发动这次袭击是为了
We strike this blow for our brothers and sisters
命丧于这个腐朽国家之手的兄弟姐妹
Who have died at the hands of this corrupt nation.
光荣的时刻已经来到
The hour is here,
我们已准备好投身到即将开始的战争
And we are ready for the war that is to come.
我们的战士们会战斗不息
Our fighters will not rest
直到美国千疮百孔
Until America lies crippled and dying,
直到街道血流成河
Her streets running with blood,
直到人民摇尾乞怜
And her people begging for mercy,
但我们不会怜悯和宽恕
But there will be none...
只有报仇雪恨
Only our vengeance.
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
怎么了
What is it?
有条子
Police.
关掉电脑  藏起来
Why don't you close down the computer and get out of sight.
把东西拆下来  看着这小的
Take everything down and watch the brother.
你得跟我来
You need to come with me.
怎么了
What is happening?
外面有两个警察
There are two police officers outside.
我要你去看看他们想干嘛
I want you to find out what they want
让他们相信这里平安无事
And convince them that everything's okay in here.
吉布安  别想试着报警
Jibraan... don't try to warn them.
好吧
Right.
首府警察
DCPD.
请开门
Open the door, please.
什么事
Yes?
吉布雷·阿尔扎利安
"Jibrain" Al-zarian?
是吉布安·阿尔扎利安
Jibraan al-zarian.
我们接到你邻居的电话
Uh, we got a call from one of your neighbors.
他们说听到你房间里有呼救声
They said they heard some yelling coming from your apartment?
看见了一些陌生人进了房间
Saw some people they didn't recognize enter the premises,
认为你们可能遇到麻烦了
Thought there might be some trouble.
没有  一切都很好
No, everything is fine.
那些是我的朋友
Those were friends of mine.
那呼救声是怎么回事呢
And what about the yelling?
我们有些争论
We got into an argument.
他们有点喝高了
They were drinking a little too much.
不过没什么事情
Uh, it was nothing.
先生  你朋友们现在在哪
Where are your friends now, sir?
因为他们太吵了  所以我要他们回去了
You know, they got too loud, so I asked them to leave.
他们不会再来了
They won't be back.
我很抱歉弄出那些噪音
I'm very sorry for the noise.
不会再有下一次了
Uh... it won't happen again.
我  我保证
I-I promise.
好吧  从现在开始声音小点就好
Okay. Just keep it down from now on.
-我会的  -晚安
- I will. - Have a good night.
晚安
You, too.
好了  我们安全了
All right, we're clear.
干得好  吉布安
You did good, Jibraan.
我们离开之前得念完这份声明
We have to finish reading this statement before we take off.
我们要去哪
Where are we going?
别担心
Don't worry about that.
只要你按我们说的做
You just keep doing as we say,
你和你弟弟
And you and your brother
就会安然无恙  懂吗
Are gonna make it through this, all right?
让他对好镜头
Set him up.
但我们不会怜悯和宽恕  只有报仇雪恨
And there will be none, only our vengeance.
而这仅仅是个开始
And this is only the beginning.
我们会以崇高和正义之名
We will strike again and again in the name
反复地进行袭击
Of all that is great and righteous.
我想我发现了一些线索
I think I've got something.
沃克探员  什么线索
Agent walker? What is it?
其中一个过滤器几分钟前标记出了这个
One of the filters flagged this a few minutes ago.
我刚检查完
I just finished vetting it.
这些是六个月来的大量存款
These are multiple deposits over a period of six months.
来自一个海外穆斯林信仰组织
From an overseas Muslim relief organization
叫做世界和平伊斯兰组织
Called the Islamic League For World Peace.
一共有2百万美金
A total of two million dollars
转账到了华盛顿大陆银行
To the Washington Continental Bank.
所有的钱都是在30分钟内转账的
Every penny of it was withdrawn within 30 minutes.
账户上是什么名字
What name's on the account?
吉布安·阿尔扎利安
Jibraan Al-Zarian.
27岁  四年前以学生签证
He's 27 years old, moved here
从巴基斯坦到这里居住
From Pakistan on student visa four years ago.
这是他的个人网络账户
This is his personal web account.
这些是他最近浏览的网页
These are some of the sites he's been looking at recently.
能找到他的地址吗
We got an address on him?
不行  这个地址是假的
No. This address is false.
根本就不存在
It doesn't exist.
对  他的签证过了期  他是非法居民
That's it, his visa expired. He's here illegally,
他应该不想被发现
And he probably doesn't want to be found.
在他移民表格里面有
He does have a personal reference
-一个担保人  -谁
- On his INS form. - Who?
木塔里·高哈
Muhtadi Gohar.
他住在乔治敦G大街的清真寺
He lives at the G street mosque in Georgetown.
他是这里的教长
He's the imam there.
他也许能帮我们找到阿尔扎利安
He might be able to help us find Al-Zarian.
我们要找他谈谈  把阿尔扎利安加入
We need to talk to him. Put out an APB
全面通缉的名单里  在内部数据库运行
On Al-Zarian, run it through the interagency database.
看你还能发现什么蛛丝马迹
See what else you can find.
把所有数据都传真到车上
Fax everything over to the car.
干得漂亮
Great work.
等等  杰克
Jack, wait.
你确信你要跟进这个案子吗
Are you sure you're up for this?
我得坚持到底
I have to see this through.
拜托了
Please.
我能帮上忙
I can help.
好吧  我们出发
Okay. Let's go.
请进
Come in.
阁下  克里尔先生来这里见您
Ma'am, Mr. Collier here to see you.
谢谢  皮尔斯探员
Thank you, Agent Pierce.
没你的事了
That'll be all.
感谢你能来  马丁
I appreciate you coming, Martin.
好久不见了  你的风采依旧
It's been a long time. You look good.
谢谢
Thanks.
奥利维亚  我知道你为什么要我来这里
So, olivia, I know why you asked me here,
但我得告诉你  要我挖出
But I have to tell you, having me dig up dirt
诺亚·丹尼尔斯的丑闻是一回事
On Noah Daniels is one thing.
但这次就完全不同了
This is a whole different animal.
这个我明白  马丁
I'm aware of that, Martin.
替我办成此事  我要你好好收拾这恶贼
I want this to happen. I want this person taken care of.
是乔纳斯·霍奇斯
It's Jonas Hodges.
-斯塔克伍德的那个吗  -是的
- Starkwood? - Yes.
你有什么理由要对付他呢
What in god's name do you have against him?
我不知道你听到了多少风声
I don't know how much of this will get out,
但霍奇斯是今天发生
But Hodges was behind everything
所有事情的主谋  从飞机的失事
That happened today, from the planes going down
一直到袭击白宫
To the attack on the White House.
-什么  -是真的
- What? - It's true.
他还该为我弟弟的死负责
He's also responsible for the death of my brother.
我以为你弟弟是自杀的
I thought your brother killed himself.
他是被谋杀的
He was murdered,
是霍奇斯亲手策划的
And Hodges was responsible.
好吧  但是为什么呢
Okay. But why?
一言难尽啊  马丁
It's complicated, Martin,
我没有时间详细解释
And I don't have time to go into it.
你要知道的就是霍奇斯拿到了协议
All you need to know is Hodges worked a deal.
证人保护协议
Witness protection.
我母亲批准了  然后他就会逍遥法外
My mother approved it, and he's going free...
除非有人出面干涉
Unless someone intervenes.
-我能给你提点建议吗  -什么
- Okay, can I give you a little advice? - What?
这次玩大了  还是少管闲事为妙
This is big game. Walk away.
我做不到
I can't do that.
这一旦成为事实
Once this happens,
一旦你成功了  你将无法回头
Once it goes through, you can never go back.
这事会在你后半生中如影随形
You will live with it for the rest of your life.
我不用你来给我做良知问题的说教
I don't need a lecture on conscience from you,
不用你们所有人来教我
Of all people.
我已经过了深思熟虑
I have thought this through.
我所不能忍受的是
What I can't live with
那个恶魔逍遥法外
Is that monster getting away with this.
他要为他的所作所为付出代价
He has to pay for what he did.
那么霍奇斯现在在哪
So, uh, where's Hodges now?
在联邦调查局的监狱里  市中心总局
In FBI custody, downtown Bureau.
那协议已经签署了
Deal has been signed.
他会在1小时之内释放
He's being released into witness protection
并转入证人保护程序
Within the hour.
这是他的行程表
Here's his itinerary.
当他走出那扇门时我们就再难对付他了
When he walks out that door, we lose him.
他会从此人间蒸发
He disappears forever.
一切要速战速决
This has got to happen fast.
马丁
Martin.
好吧
All right.
我去打电话
I'll make a call.
我会给你联系方式  价钱
I'll get you contact information, a price,
还有你如何转账的说明
And instructions on how to transfer the funds.
谢谢
Thank you.
我会很快答复你的
You'll hear from me soon.
霍奇斯先生
Mr. Hodges,
这是美国沙利文警官
This is U.S. Marshal Sullivan.
我正将你转移到他的监管下
I'm placing you in his custody.
他会将你转到证人保护组
He'll take you to witness protection.
谢谢你的热情款待  女士
Thank you for your hospitality, young lady.
这文件概述了你的新身份
This dossier outlines your new identity,
你的新住所
Your new place of residence,
你需要改头换面的所有信息
All the information you're going to need to make this transition.
罗伯特·蒂皮特吗  我的新名字吗
Robert Tippett? That's my new name?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
听起来像狗狗的名字
Sounds like a dog breed.
我们第一站是在科罗拉多州证人保护机构
Our first stop is the Witt-Sec facility in Colorado.
我们会完成您的新档案的最后一步
We'll put the finishing touches on your new biography,
制作你的新身份证明
Fabricate your new ID,
让你去做心理咨询
Get you into counseling.
心理咨询
Counseling?
那有助于您应付新环境中的问题
It helps entrants deal with their new circumstances.
孩子  你知道我是谁吗
Son, you know who I am.
我给你的印象像一个需要心理治疗
Do I impress you as someone who needs therapy
才能应付新环境的人吗
To cope with new circumstances?
如果您需要  就能有这项服务  先生
The service is available if you want it, sir,
这是对美国纳税人的尊重
Courtesy of the American taxpayer.
你以为我被从轻发落了  是吗
You think I'm getting off easy, don't you?
我没有任何想法
I don't think anything.
我是你肚里的蛔虫  孩子
I can smell attitude, son,
你肚里有几根花花肠子清楚得很
And you're giving it off pretty thick.
我已经一无所有
I've lost everything--
我的公司  我的家庭
My company, my family,
最重要的是我的姓名
And most importantly, my name.
你明白要花多少血汗
Do you know how much blood and sweat went
才能使那名字永垂青史吗
Into making that name mean something?
我们在30分钟后前往安德鲁斯空军基地
We leave for Andrews Air Force base in 30 minutes.
我想你该做好准备
I suggest you get ready.
杰克
Jack?
我没事
I'm fine.
你干嘛  我们甚至不知道他们干了什么
What are you doing? We don't even know that they've done anything yet.
他们可能是无辜的
They could be innocent.
无辜的  你听到霍奇斯说的
Innocent? You heard Hodges.
他们会利用本土恐怖分子来进行这些袭击
They're gonna use sleeper cells to carry out these attacks.
阿尔扎利安可能不是今天发生
Al-zarian might not have been knowingly complicit
一切的蓄意同谋者
About everything that happened today,
但要说无辜的话  不可能
But innocent? No.
是谁
Yes?
我是联邦调查局的沃克探员
This is agent Walker with FBI.
高哈先生
Mr. Gohar?
是的
Yes.
很抱歉这么晚打扰您
We're sorry to bother you at such a late hour,
但我们需要你的协助
But we need your help.
我的协助
My help?
阻止一起潜在的恐怖袭击
To stop a potential terrorist attack.
高哈先生
Mr. Gohar?
我认识你
I know you.
我叫杰克·鲍尔
My name is jack bauer.
当然
Of course.
我在电视上看到你出庭作证了
I watched your testimony on television.
先生 我们能进去说话吗
Sir. Can we talk to you inside?
劳驾
Please.
你们想干嘛
What do you want?
我们在找一个在这里朝拜的人
We're looking for a man who worships here.
我们怀疑他可能
We believe he may be
在协助进行另一起恐怖袭击
Helping to plan another attack
而且很快会在特区发生
That may be happening soon, in D.C.
我知道这种指责最终会落到我们头上
I knew the blame would eventually fall on us.
他叫吉布安·阿尔扎利安
His name is Jibraan Al-Zarian.
你认识他吗
Do you know him?
你们为什么怀疑他是恐怖分子呢
And why do you think he's a terrorist?
他符合一些犯罪特征的剖析
He fits a specific profile.
你是说他是穆斯林
You mean, he is a muslim.
他是巴基斯坦人
He's a pakistani national.
他签证一年前过期
His visa lapsed a year ago.
他没有合法住址
And he has no legal address.
他在移民表格中填的担保人是你
He listed you as a personal reference on his INS form.
在哪里做礼拜是个人隐私  受法律保护
Where someone worships is private information, protected by law.
目前为止  找到阿尔扎利安
Right now, finding al-zarian
是阻止恐怖袭击的唯一方式
Is the only way we're going to prevent an attack against civilians.
那么  我再问你一遍  你认识他吗
So, I ask you again, sir, do you know him?
看照片
Look at the photo!
是的  我认识他
Yes, I know him.
但他不是恐怖分子
But he is not a terrorist!
你凭什么这么肯定
What makes you so sure?
吉布安向我讨教精神层面的问题很多次了
Jibraan has come to me many times for spiritual advice.
我了解这个人
I know the man.
他并不暴力  也不是极端分子
He is not violent and he is not an extremist.
可我们有证据表明他是
We have evidence that indicates otherwise.
我倒想看看你们所谓的证据
I would like to see this evidence.
听着
Listen to me.
我们来不是要和你争论这个问题
We did not come here to debate this with you.
他住在哪里
Where does he live?
我不知道他住哪里
I don't know where he lives.
-他在哪里上班  -我也不清楚
- Where does he work? - I don't know that, either.
鬼才会相信你
And I don't believe you!
那么我该相信你吗
But you expect me to believe you?
我看了你在参议院的听证会
I watched your hearing at the senate,
我知道你做过什么
I know what you have done.
所以你告诉我我为什么要相信你说的一切
So, tell me why should I believe anything you say to me?
首先  你别无选择
First because you don't have a choice.
其次  我告诉你的都是事实
Second, because I am telling you the truth!
事实就是你带着莫须有的消息
The truth is that you come into a house of worship
闯入我的礼拜堂
With information you should not have,
肆无忌惮的指控  没有合法文件
An outrageous accusation, no legal warrant,
还威胁我
and threaten me.
我没有威胁你
I have not threatened you.
暂时还没
Not yet.
但我们都知道接下来会发生什么
But we both know where this is going.
如果你这么确定他是清白的
If you're so sure he's innocent,
-为什么不敢说他在哪里呢  -杰克
- Why are you afraid to tell us where he is? - Jack...
他在哪里
Where is he?!
我说过了  我不知道
I told you, I don't know.
即便我知道  我也不会说
But even if i did, I would say nothing.
我不会帮助你们逮捕无辜的人
I would not help you arrest an innocent man.
我是沃克探员
This is agent Walker.
我是詹尼斯
It's Janis.
一名首府警察15分钟前
A DCPD officer recognized Jibraan Al-zarian
接到一通报告家庭暴力的电话
From a domestic disturbance call
里面涉及吉布安·阿尔扎利安
He took 15 minutes ago.
地址是东布鲁克街2700号
The address is 2700 eastbrook,
3号公寓
Apartment 3.
很好  继续和首府警局协作
All right, good. Coordinate with DCPD.
设置包围圈  监控整幢大楼
Set up an envelope and put the building under surveillance
我们10分钟后到
We'll be there in 10 minutes.
我们有阿尔扎利安的地址了
We have an address on Al-zarian.
-杰克  我们走  -转过身去
- Let's go, Jack. - Turn around.
-为什么  -我让你转过去
- Why? - I said turn around.
-举起手来  -杰克
- Put your hands up, now! - Jack?
你在做什么  杰克
What are you doing, Jack?
我不会让他在我们到达前
I'm not letting him call Al-zarian
给阿尔扎利安通风报信的
Before we get there.
-他得跟我们一起去  -你没那个权利
- He's coming with us. - You have no right!
-我又没干坏事  -闭嘴
- I have done nothing wrong! - Shut up!
我们没有怜悯和宽恕  只有报仇雪恨
...there will be none, only our vengeance.
而这仅仅是个开始
And this is only the beginning.
我们会以崇高和正义之名
We will strike again and again
发动一次又一次的袭击
In the name of all that is great and righteous.
好  好吧
All right, fine.
运输队已经准备好  就等我们了
The staging team's ready and waiting on us.
2分钟后就上传好了
This'll be uploaded in two minutes.
很好
Good.
吉布安
Jibraan...
准备出发了
We're getting ready to move out.
你得和你弟弟谈一下
I'm gonna need you to talk to your brother.
照我们讨论的说给他听
Tell him what we discussed.
去把他叫醒
Go ahead and wake him up.
求你了  我不能这么做
Please, I can't do this.
不  你能
Yes, you can.
你必须做
And you will.
我怎么知道你们事后不会杀了哈米德
How do I know you won't kill Hamid anyway?
因为我们还需要他告诉警察
Because we need him to tell the police
他哥哥是恐怖分子
That his brother's a terrorist.
相信我
Believe me,
你这么做是救了他
You're saving his life by doing this.
好了  快点  出发了
Now, come on, let's go.
哈米德  哈米德  别慌
Hamid, Hamid, calm down.
别怕
Don't be scared.
吉布安  怎么回事
Jibraan, what is this?
抱歉以这种方式对你
Sorry we had to do it this way.
可我们不会伤害你的  明白吗
But you're not going to be hurt anymore, okay?
我们  我们是谁
We? Who is we?
出什么事了
What's happening?
我来解释这一切  好吗
I'll explain everything to you, okay?
他是谁
Who's he?
他是我朋友
Um, he's a friend.
你朋友吗  你朋友我都认识
Your friend? I know all your friends.
可我从没见过他
I've never seen him before.
那是因为我没把他介绍给你
That's because I have kept him from you.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我得告诉你一些事情
I have to tell you something.
我其实不是你想的那样
I'm not the person you think I am.
什么
What?
我憎恨这个国家对我们的人民所做的一切
I hate what this country has done to our people.
我和这些人一起工作
And I'm working with these men.
他们会帮助我
They're going to help me strike back
向那些欺侮我们的恶势力发动反击
Against the evil that has been done to us.
反击
Strike back?
我不能透露更多的了
I can't say any more than that.
我不相信
I don't believe it.
这个国家收留我们  让我们安居于此
This country brought us in, gave us a home,
这才是你挂在嘴边的话
That's what you always said.
是的  但那是个谎言
Yeah, that was a lie.
我以前一直没告诉你我内心的愤怒
I have been protecting you from this rage I've always felt inside.
但现在是时候让你知道真相了
But now it is time for you to know the truth.
我们的父母死在美国人手上  哈米德
It was the Americans who killed our parents, Hamid.
我要让他们付出代价
I'm going to make them pay.
你对我哥做了什么
What have you done to my brother?
你给他洗脑了吗  这根本就不是我哥
You've poisoned his mind! This isn't my brother!
他们并没对我做什么
They have not done anything to me, okay.
重要的是你得明白我说的话
It is very important you accept what I'm saying to you.
你干嘛要告诉我这些
Why are you telling me this?
若有人问你我的动机
When they ask you why I did what I did,
我希望你能告诉他们
I want you to tell them.
没人会怪你的
Okay, no one will blame you for anything.
你并没有做错
You have done nothing wrong.
我知道你很难理解这一切
I know this is very difficult for you to understand.
但以后你会明白的
But over time, you will see.
我爱你  哈米德
I love you, Hamid.
你说今天当一个穆斯林是糟糕的一天
You said today was a bad day to be a muslim.
现在看来  当你弟弟更加糟糕
Well, it's an even worse day to be your brother.
好了  该走了
All right, let's go.
集结待命地区准备好了
Staging area's ready.
你留下来处理一下
You stay here and finish up.
知道了
Understood.
吉布安  不要这样做
Jibraan, don't do this.
一切就绪了吗
Everything set?
他弟弟相信了吗
Yeah, was the brother convinced?
还不确定
I'm not sure.
即便他不相信
But even if he wasn't,
袭击一旦发生  他就会相信的
Once the attack happens, he will be.
走吧
Let's go.
喂
Hello?
马丁·克里尔说你在等我电话
Yes, yes, martin collier said you'd be expecting my call.
他给了我目标的行程
He gave me the target's itinerary.
我正要去
I'm set to go.
好的  那么  条件可以接受了
Good. good, so the terms are acceptable.
是的
They are.
我只是需要你转账
I just need you to transfer the funds.
账号多少
What's the account number?
国际银行号码是
International banking code is
V6B1B1
Victor-six-bravo-one-bravo-one.
账号  0599072477
Account number 0599072477.
资金转账后  我会行动的
After the funds have been transferred, I'll proceed.
我们没必要再联系了
There'll be no need for us to have any further contact.
好吧  可是你
All right, but what are you--
请进
Yes?
打扰一下  泰勒女士
Excuse me, Ms. Taylor.
你父亲要见你
I thought you should know your father has asked to see you.
我父亲在这里吗
My father's here?
考虑到可能的生化武器袭击
In light of the potential bioweapon attack,
总统下令让他搬到白宫来以防万一
The president ordered him moved to the white house for his safety.
谢谢你  亚伦
Thank you, Aaron.
我还有些事情要处理
I just have something to take care of.
告诉他们我马上过去
Tell them I'll be right there.
好的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
我是马丁·克里尔
You've reached Martin Collier.
有事请留言
Please leave a message.
马丁  我是奥利维亚·泰勒
Martin, it's Olivia Taylor.
我跟你找的人谈过了
I spoke to the contact,
但没有谈成
But I couldn't go through with it.
我决定采取你的建议不管这事了
I decided to take your advice and walk away.
请尽快和我联系
Please call me as soon as you can.
我是鲍尔
This is Bauer.
杰克  我是克罗伊  我发现
Jack, it's Chloe, I found something
吉布安·阿尔扎利安的事有些蹊跷
Weird about these hits on Jibraan Al-zarian.
说下去
Go ahead.
我告诉过你他的账户
You know how I said that the two million dollars
在6个月内
Was deposited into his account
总共存入了2百万美元
Over a period of six months?
那不对  时间被提前了
Well, that wasn't right. They were backdated.
什么意思
What do you mean?
一种回溯算法捕捉到了一个差异
One of the trace algorithms caught a discrepancy,
那些钱实际上是在30分钟前存入的
All that money was really just deposited 30 minutes ago.
他浏览过的那些极端分子网站呢
What about the extremist websites he was visiting?
时间标记也是一样的情况
Same thing with the time stamps.
网站访问时间是在30分钟前被修改提前的
The hits were backdated 30 minutes ago.
你完全肯定吗
Are you absolutely positive?
看起来是这样
It looks that way.
吉布安很可能是无辜的
Jibraan could be innocent.
知道了  谢谢
Okay, thanks.
杰克  什么事
What's going on, Jack?
克罗伊找到证据表明吉布安是被陷害的
Chloe found evidence that Jibraan is being set up.
被人栽赃了
He's been framed.
阿尔梅达为什么要嫁祸一个无辜的人
Why would Almeida frame an innocent man?
因为一旦袭击不顺利
Because they wouldn't want to risk the attack
他们冒不起那个险
Not being carried out properly.
我怎么这么笨呢
How could I be so stupid?
一个无辜的人更容易掌控
An innocent man is so much easier to control.
他们需要的只是一个穆斯林
All they needed was a muslim,
他们可以给他伪造任何背景
They could create whatever background they wanted.
把手给我
Give me your hands.
我很吃惊
I am surprised.
为什么  你是对的
Why? You were right.
不是关于吉布安
Not about Jibraan.
就我对当局的经验来看
My experience with the authorities,
警方一定会使出浑身解数
The police is that they will go to any lengths
对他们的错误矢口否认
Not to admit they were wrong.
即使是以牺牲一个无辜生命为代价
Even at the expense of an Innocent man's life.
至少你没有这么做
At least you didn't do that.
请明白我原谅你了
Please know that I forgive you.
我不是在祈求你的谅解
I'm not asking for your forgiveness.
但我希望至少你可以原谅自己
Then i hope you can at least forgive yourself.
我早就对此不抱希望了
I gave up on that a long time ago.
鲍尔先生  信仰上帝为时不晚啊
It's never to late to turn towards god, Mr. Bauer.
-够了吗  -是的  谢谢
- That's enough? - Yeah, thanks.
谢谢
Thank you.
你不用在这陪着我  艾莉
You don't need to stay with me, Ally.
他们需要我的时候会来找我的
But they know where to find me if they need me.
我觉得让你了解当前局势
I thought it was important for you to hear what's going on.
还有我这么做的原因是很必要的
And for you to understand why I did what I did.
宝贝  你是总统你做主
You're the president, sweetheart.
你不需要向我解释
You don't owe me an explanation.
宝贝女儿
There's my girl.
爸爸
Hi, dad.
利维  你可以抱得再紧些
Livy, you can squeeze a bit harder.
我没那么脆弱
I won't break.
哦  我不行了
Oh, I might!
抱歉我没能及时赶到医院
I'm sorry I couldn't come to the hospital.
别傻了
Don't be silly.
你是上帝派来助你妈妈一臂之力的天使
You're a godsend being here helping your mom.
能看到你们言归于好
Just knowing you two were speaking again,
甚至可以同舟共济  这就足够了
Let alone working together, that's enough.
亨利  我不确定我们彼此的信任
Henry, I'm not sure that our déente
能否撑过当前的局势
Is holding at the moment.
奥利维亚  你妈妈告诉我
Olivia, your mother told me
她与乔纳斯·霍奇斯所定的协议
About the deal she made with Jonas Hodges.
而且我也能理解
And I know you, understandably,
你对这一协议的强烈反对
Have serious concerns about that.
我想了很久
Well, I've had some time to think.
如果我站在妈妈的立场上
To put myself in mom's position.
客观来讲
To be objective
从现实情况分析
And pragmatic--
这是一个英明的领袖
The way a good leader should be.
应该做出的决定
Has to be.
我知道这个决定对你来说是一场折磨
I know that decision was horrible for you.
但是我确能理解
But I do understand.
我对自己的鲁莽决定深表歉意
I'm sorry I made the choice even harder.
总有一天乔纳斯·霍奇斯将面对公正的审判
Jonas Hodges will face judgment one day.
即便此生不能  必在来世
If not in this life, in the next.
蒂皮特先生
Mr. Tippet.
抱歉
Oh. sorry.
我需要一点时间来适应这个名字
It's going to take me a little while to get used to that.
这是人之常情
Always does.
我需要将那钱包充公
I'll need to confiscate the wallet.
我们不能让您持有任何
We can't let you hold on to anything
与您以前生活联系起来的东西
That ties you to your former life.
还有那相片
And the picture.
你喜欢你的工作吗  沙利文先生
You like your job, Mr. Sullivan?
很有挑战性
It has its challenges.
你给我的印象
You strike me as someone
是一位不甘于转移囚犯之职的人
who wouldn't be totally satisfied ferrying prisoners around.
我不打算一辈子干这行
I don't plan on doing this my entire life.
很高兴听你这么说
Good to hear that.
也许你我有朝一日可以同朝共事
Maybe you and I can do some work together some day.
先生
Sir?
我不打算一辈子充当蒂皮特先生
I don't intend to be Mr. Tippet forever.
在这里签名确认转移
Sign here acknowledging transfer.
联邦调查局确认了
FBI's identified
那个要实施生化武器袭击者的身份
The man they believe is going to carry out e bioweapon's attack.
杰克·鲍尔和沃克探员在去找他的路上
Jack Bauer and agent Walker are on their way
前往一个他可能在的地点
To a possible location for him.
他们有没有找到任何线索能表明
Have they found out anything that would give us an idea of the target--
-攻击目标或者时间表的  -暂时没有
- Or a timetable? - No.
目前为止  没有什么实际的
Nothing actionable. Not yet.
总统阁下  我接个电话
Um, Madam president.
你确信吗
Are you sure?
是怎么发生的
How did this happen?
一旦你了解到更多  立刻打电话给我
Call me as soon as you know more.
什么事  蒂姆
What is it, Tim?
乔纳斯·霍奇斯刚刚被杀了
Jonas Hodges was just killed.
-什么  怎么回事  -汽车炸弹
- What? How? - Car bomb.
在他刚离开联邦调查局的时候
As he was leaving FBI.
他们还知道些什么
What else do they know?
-有疑犯吗  -还没有
- Are there any suspects? - Not yet.
失陪接个电话
Um, excuse me.
我认为是内鬼做的
My guess is this was an inside job.
内鬼
Inside job?
无论是谁下令杀他的
Whoever ordered the hit
他一定知道霍奇斯转移的确切时间和地点
Knew exactly when and where hodges was being transported.
见鬼
Damn it!
蒂姆  优先处理这件事
Tim, get on top of this.
我想知道究竟是怎么回事
I want to know exactly how this happened.
遵命  阁下
Yes, ma'am.
泰勒女士
Ms. Taylor,
一切还好吗
Is everything all right?
一切都好
Oh, it's fine.
我一会就回来
I'll be right back.
喂
Yeah?
霍奇斯死了
Hodges is dead!
冷静
Okay, calm down.
我们不该在电话里谈论的
We shouldn't be talking on the phone.
你不明白
You don't understand,
这里有个致命的失误
There's been a terrible mistake.
我跟那个你给我号码的人说过话
I spoke to the man whose number you gave me.
但我扛不起这个失误
But I didn't go through with it.
我不能
I couldn't.
难道你没收到我的短信吗
Didn't you get my message?
奥利维亚  我叫你冷静
Olivia, I said calm down.
我办不到
I can't!
霍奇斯死了  现在我难逃干系了
Hodges is dead and I'm responsible.
我们不能在电话里说这些话
We cannot have this conversation over the phone.
你明白吗  你有没有意识到
Do you understand? Do you realize
如果这些话泄露出去我会有什么下场吗
What could happen to me if this gets out?!
奥利维亚  你现在该闭上嘴了
Olivia, you need to stop talking now.
听到我说了吗
Do you hear me?
深呼吸  听我说
Take a deep breath, listen to me.
我们挂掉电话  好吗
All right, we'll hang up, okay?
好的
All right.
好的  我在听
Okay, I'm listening.
好的
Okay.
你能去珀欣公园吗
Can you get to Pershing Park?
不行  现在不行
No, not right now.
我正在和我母亲开会
I'm in a meeting with my mother.
好吧  我会等的  你尽快赶到那里
Fine. I'll wait. Get there as fast as you can.
然后我们当面谈
We'll talk about this face-to-face.
好吗
Okay?
好吧
All right.
谢谢你  亚伦
Thank you, Aaron.
什么情况  探员
What do you have, agent?
武装分子在里屋  持有一名人质
Armed hostile in the back room, holding a hostage.
有阿尔梅达的消息吗
What about Almeida?
他不在里面
He's not in there.
自己看吧  里德
See for yourself. Reed,
-给我们换个视角  -遵命  长官
- Give us another look. - Yes, sir.
镜头向人质方向拉近
Move in closer on the hostage.
那是你们要找的人吗
Is that who you're looking for?
不是
No.
那是吉布安的弟弟  哈米德
That's Jibraan's brother, Hamid.
他们以他来要挟  要求吉布安
They're using him as leverage, to make Jibraan
听他们的话
Do what they want.
因为若是我也会这么干
'cause that's what I would've done.
探员  一定要确保人质安全
Agent, it is imperative that we take this hostile alive.
现在  他是我们找到
Right now, he's our only shot at finding out
袭击地点的唯一希望
Where this attack is going taking place.
明白  我已经通知了我的手下
Understood. I've already informed my men.
我希望亲自行动  可以吗
I want to run point on this. Is that all right?
谢谢
Thanks.
你要留在这里
You're going to stay here
和后备队员一起
With the backup teams.
你觉得这是个好主意吗
Are you sure that's such a good idea?
怎么了
What?
鲍尔探员  他看起来不太好
Agent Bauer-- he doesn't seem to be too well.
-也许该你来指挥  -我正在指挥
- Maybe you should be in charge. - I am.
杰克被生化武器感染了
Jack was infected with the bioweapon.
就是他们准备用来袭击的那种武器
The same one that they are going to use in this attack.
那么他应该留在医院里
Then he should be in the hospital.
没有治疗方法的
There is no treatment.
他可能没有一天的命可活
He probably has less than a day to live.
如果他足够坚强的话  相信我
So if he is strong enough, trust me,
他是做这个的最佳人选
He's the best person for this job.
抱歉
I'm sorry,
我开始不知道
I didn't realize.
沃克探员  我们准备好了
Agent Walker, we're ready.
鲍尔先生  请你
Please, Mr. Bauer,
竭尽全力营救哈米德
Do what you can to save Hamid.
我们检查了窗户
We've checked the windows.
我们有个明确的办法
We have a clear approach.
-出发  -探员们和高哈先生呆在一起
- Let's go. - Agents, stay with Mr. Gohar.
听我数
On my count.
三  二  一
Three... two... one.
哈米德  住手
Hamid, stop!
把那放下
Put it down.
我们是联邦调查局  我们需要他活着
We're FBI. We need him alive.
-把那放下  -他害我哥成了恐怖分子
- Put it down. - He made my brother into a terrorist.
你哥哥不是恐怖分子  他是无辜的
Your brother is not a terrorist. He's innocent.
我们知道  他是被陷害的
We know that. He's being set up.
-他是被逼的  -什么
- He's being forced to do this. Please. - What?
那个人是唯一能
The only one who can tell us
告诉我们你哥哥在哪的人
Where your brother is that man right there.
现在把那放下
Now put it down.
站起来  把手放在脑后
Stand up now, put your hands behind your head.
快点
Do it!
沃克探员  快去
Agent Walker, move in now.
快走  坐在床上
Move! On the bed
见鬼  他失血过多  需要医生  快
Damn it, he's bleeding out. We need a medic, now!
现场需要医护队
We need a med team on site.
坐在那儿
Sit right there.
你进入了系统吗
Are you in their system?
我已经进入了主要安全线路了
I've tapped into the main security trunk line,
但我仍在迂回破解  确保
But I'm still looping in breakers to make sure
我们的进入不被标记上
The tap doesn't get flagged.
好吧  我们现在有时间表限制
All right, well, we're on a timetable here.
还需要多长时间
How much longer is it going to take?
10分钟  也许15分钟
Ten, maybe 15 minutes.
把那包给我
Hand me that case.
你们要我做什么
What are you going to have me do?
你马上就会知道的
You'll find out soon enough.
地铁准时吗
Is the subway on schedule?
是的  准时
Yeah, it's on schedule.